fxcoliseum.com 2016-11-28

# Privacy Policy - fxcoliseum.com

#### Security and Disclosure

FX-Coliseum considers your privacy as our upmost concerns and we respect each individual's right of privacy. We value our relationship with you, and we take pride in maintaining loyalty and respect with each individual Customer by providing you with security. The provisions of this notice apply to former Customers as well as our current Customers. 

#### Personal Information

When you apply for or maintain a live account with FX-Coliseum, we have to collect personal information about you for business purposes, such as evaluating your financial needs, processing your requests and transactions, informing you about our products and services that may be of interest to you, and providing customer service. Such information may include: 

  * Application information:

Information you provide to us on applications and other forms, such as your name, address, birth date, Social Security number, occupation, assets, and income. 

  * Transaction information:

Information about your transactions with us and with our affiliates as well as information about our communications with you. Examples include your account balances, trading activity, your inquiries, and our responses. 

  * Verification information:

This relates to Information necessary to verify your identity such as passport or driver's license. Examples also include background information about you we receive from public records or from other entities not affiliated with FX-Coliseum. 

#### About Cookies

Cookies are files containing information that a Web site uses to track its visitors. FX-Coliseum may set and access FX-Coliseum cookies on your computer, enabling us to learn which advertisements and promotions bring users to our Web site. FX-Coliseum or any of its divisions may use cookies in connection with FX-Coliseum products and services to track your activities on our Web sites. Such information that we collect and share would be anonymous and not personally identifiable. 

#### Security Technology

FX-Coliseum is equipped with Secure Socket Layer (SSL) encryption technology in order to protect certain information that you submitting to us. This type of technology protects you from having your information intercepted by anyone other than FX-Coliseum while it is being transmitted to us. We always aggressive to ensure that our Web sites are secure and meeting the industry standard. We also utilize other safeguards such as firewalls, authentication systems (e.g., passwords and personal identification numbers), and access control mechanisms to control unauthorized access to systems and data. 

#### Sharing Information with Our Affiliates

We may share your personal information described above with our affiliates for business purposes, such as, but not limited to, servicing customer accounts and informing customers about new products and services, or to aid in the trading activity of the company, its affiliates, or employees, and as permitted by applicable law. Our affiliates may include companies controlled or owned by us as well as companies that have an ownership interest in our company. The information we share with affiliates may include any of the information described above, such as your name, address, and trading and account information. Our affiliates maintain the privacy of your information to the same extent FX-Coliseum does in accordance with this Policy. 

#### Sharing Information with Third Parties

FX-Coliseum does not disclose your personal information to third parties, except as described in this Policy. Third party disclosures may include sharing such information with non-affiliated companies that perform support services for your account or facilitate your transactions with FX-Coliseum, including those that provide professional, legal, or accounting advice to FX-Coliseum. Non-affiliated companies that assist FX-Coliseum in providing services to you are required to maintain the confidentiality of such information to the extent they receive it and to use your personal information only in the course of providing such services and only for the purposes that FX-Coliseum dictates. 

We may also disclose your personal information to third parties to fulfill your instructions or pursuant to your expressed consent. As we can guarantee, your personal information will not be sold under any circumstances.
